all:
Aye, aye, Captain!
全部：
是啊是啊，队长！
- I can't hear you.
- 我听不到你说话。
all:
Aye, aye, Captain!
全部：
是啊是啊，队长！
- * Ohh... *
-*哦...*
* Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? *
*谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ *
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
- * Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he *
- * 吸水性和黄色
他是多孔的*
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
- * If nautical nonsense
be something you wish *
- *如果航海废话
成为你所希望的*
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
- * Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish *
- * 然后落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通 *
all: SpongeBob SquarePants!
所有：海绵宝宝！
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
SpongeBob SquarePants!
- SpongeBob
- 海绵宝宝
SquarePants!
方裤！
* *
**
- Ah, I don't know
what I love more, Squidward,
- 啊，我不知道
我更喜欢什么，章鱼哥，
feeding people Krabby Patties
during the day,
给人们喂蟹肉饼
白天，
or cleaning up
their mess at night.
或清理
他们晚上的混乱。
Are you kidding me?
你在开玩笑吧？
Look at all this garbage
看看这些垃圾
those animals left behind.
那些留下来的动物。
Hm.
- One man's garbage...
嗯。
- 一个人的垃圾...
So much gum!
这么多口香糖！
Ooh, this is gonna be fun.
哦，这会很有趣。
Ooh-wah!
- Ow!
哦，哇！
- 噢！
Hey, watch it--
嘿，注意看——
* *
**
Ah! Urchin!
啊!顽童！
- That's no urchin,
it's a Krabby Patty.
- 这不是顽童，
这是蟹肉饼。
- Yuck. A rotten Krabby Patty.
- 恶心。腐烂的蟹肉饼。
- Wait, Squidward!
- 等等，章鱼哥！
You can't throw out
a Krabby Patty.
你不能扔掉
蟹肉饼。
That is just wrong.
- But this one is rotten.
那是错误的。
- 但是这个已经烂了。
- Oh, simple Squidward...
- 哦，简单的章鱼哥……
- No Krabby Patty
can ever truly be rotten.
- 没有蟹肉饼
可能真的会腐烂。
Here, look...
在这里，看...
- Ah!
- 啊！
- Mmm...
- 嗯...
- Oh, that looks delicious.
- 哦，看起来很好吃。
Why don't you take
another bite?
你为什么不采取
再咬一口？
- No thanks.
- 不，谢谢。
Uh, it's so delicious, I think
I'll save the rest for later.
嗯，我觉得很好吃
剩下的我会留着以后用。
No, Patty,
you stay where you are.
不，帕蒂，
你留在原地。
- Are you doing all right
there, friend?
- 你还好吗
在那里，朋友？
- Oh, I--I'm all right.
- 哦，我 - 我没事。
Yoo
尤
- Why, I'm your
new best friend.
- 为什么，我是你的
新最好的朋友。
You can call me Cuddle E. Hugs.
你可以叫我 Cuddle E. Hugs。
* *
**
I like the sound of that.
我喜欢那个声音。
- Then bring it in
for the real deal!
- 然后把它带进来
真正的交易！
Whee!
哎哟！
- That's what I call a hug.
- 这就是我所说的拥抱。
- Of course it is!
- 当然是！
Hugs is my last name,
after all.
拥抱是我的姓氏
毕竟。
- So tender.
- I try.
- 如此温柔。
- 我试试。
But enough of this.
How about you show
但这已经够了。
你展示一下怎么样
your new best friend
around town?
你最好的新朋友
城镇周围？
- You got it, Cuddle E. Hugs.
- 你明白了，拥抱 E. 拥抱。
Wow!
哇！
* *
**
all:
全部：
What a great night!
多么美好的夜晚啊！
- Oh, hey, Gary.
- 哦，嘿，加里。
Say hello to my new best
friend, Cuddle E. Hugs.
向我的最佳新人问好
朋友，拥抱E。拥抱。
- A pleasure.
- 很高兴。
- Come on, Gary. Bed time.
- Meow!
- 来吧，加里。就寝时间。
- 喵！
- Mm! Ooh!
- Here's my room!
- 毫米！哦！
- 这是我的房间！
You can take the bed,
if you want.
可以把床拿走，
如果你愿意的话。
- Nonsense. We can share it!
- 废话。我们可以分享！
- Ow.
- 噢。
Looks like your friend
Cuddle E. Hugs
看起来像你的朋友
拥抱 E. 拥抱
needs to lay off the snacks.
需要戒掉零食。
But no need to worry,
SpongeBob,
但无需担心，
海绵宝宝，
I got your new bed right here.
- Ha! Ha!
我在这里给你准备了新床。
- 哈！哈!
Whoo-hoo! Hooray!
呼呼！万岁！
You are the absolute best
at snuggles.
你绝对是最好的
依偎着。
- I didn't get the first name
Cuddle for nothing.
- 我不知道名字
无缘无故地抱抱。
How'd you sleep, Cuddle E.?
你睡得怎么样，卡德尔·E？
Oh, good morning, Gary.
哦，早上好，加里。
Hey, have you seen
Cuddle E. Hugs anywhere?
嘿嘿，你见过吗
在任何地方拥抱E.拥抱？
Aw, what if I never
see him again
噢，如果我永远不会怎么办？
再次见到他
or feel his furry embrace?
或者感受他毛茸茸的拥抱？
Maybe a bite of Krabby Patty
will make me feel better.
也许咬一口蟹肉饼
会让我感觉好一些。
- Meow...
- 喵...
I don't feel so good.
我感觉不太好。
I must miss Cuddle
more than I thought.
我一定想念卡德尔
比我想象的还要多。
- And I miss you.
You're still here.
- 我想念你。
你还在这里。
- Of course I am.
- Yee-hee!
- 我当然是。
- 呀嘿！
- Aw. Wow!
- 噢。哇！
That kiss was even more tender
than the first one.
那个吻更加温柔
比第一个。
- I've been practicing.
- 我一直在练习。
It's our ability to give
tender head kisses
这是我们的能力给予
温柔的头吻
that separates us from the
lower life forms, SpongeBob.
使我们与
低等生命形式，海绵宝宝。
Come here.
过来吧。
- So, best friend,
what should we do today?
- 那么，最好的朋友，
今天我们应该做什么？
- You should meet
my other friends.
- 你应该见面
我的其他朋友。
They are gonna love you.
他们会爱你的。
- I already love them!
- 我已经爱他们了！
- Meow...
- 喵...
- Oh--ooh, there's my buddy,
Squidward!
- 哦-哦，这是我的朋友，
章鱼哥！
- You're gonna love him.
- 你会爱他的。
He's funny and nice
and very polite.
他很有趣又友善
而且非常有礼貌。
Hey, Squidward!
嘿，章鱼哥！
Hi!
你好！
I said hey, Squidward!
我说嘿，章鱼哥！
- Please get out of my way,
and stop talking to me.
- 请别挡我的路
别跟我说话了。
- See, Cuddle E.,
he said please.
- 看，卡德尔·E.，
他说请。
I told you he was polite.
我告诉过你他很有礼貌。
- My new best friend.
Wanted you to meet him.
- 我最好的新朋友。
想让你见见他。
I don't have time
for your stupid games.
我没有时间
为了你愚蠢的游戏。
Now move it!
- Ah!
现在就动起来吧！
- 啊！
Sorry about that.
对此感到抱歉。
I--I don't know
what's gotten into him today.
我——我不知道
他今天怎么了。
- No need to be sorry,
SpongeBob.
- 无需抱歉，
海绵宝宝。
I'm your best friend!
我是你最好的朋友！
- Aw, your furry tummy
feels like home.
- 噢，你毛茸茸的肚子
感觉就像在家一样。
- Hey, SpongeBob,
why are you hugging the air?
- 嘿，海绵宝宝，
你为什么拥抱空气？
- Hey, Patrick,
I'm not hugging the air.
- 嘿，帕特里克，
我没有拥抱空气。
I'm hugging Cuddle E. Hugs.
我正在拥抱 Cuddle E. Hugs。
- Uh, mm...
- 呃，嗯……
Are you playing
some kind of trick on me?
你在玩吗
对我有什么诡计吗？
There's no one there.
那里没有人。
- Course there's someone here.
He's my new best friend.
- 当然有人在这里。
他是我最好的新朋友。
But I'm your best friend.
但我是你最好的朋友。
- Oh, yes, you are,
but so is Cuddle E. Hugs,
- 哦，是的，你是，
但 Cuddle E. Hugs 也是如此，
and I have enough love
in my heart for both of you.
我有足够的爱
在我心里为你们俩。
No!
不！
I want all your love!
我想要你全部的爱！
Give me it!
给我吧！
SpongeBob's my best friend!
海绵宝宝是我最好的朋友！
Mine!
矿！
Give me his love!
给我他的爱吧！
No! No, no!
不！不，不！
He looks madder
than a rattlesnake
他看上去更生气了
比响尾蛇
in a room full of
rocking chairs.
在一个充满了
摇椅。
- I just tried to introduce him
to my friend, Cuddle E. Hugs,
- 我只是想介绍他
致我的朋友 Cuddle E. Hugs，
and he went crazy!
他疯了！
In fact,
everyone's acting weird.
事实上，
每个人都表现得很奇怪。
They're all pretending
they can't see him.
他们都在假装
他们看不到他。
- Well, where is
this new friend of yours?
- 那么，在哪里
你的这位新朋友？
- Oh, not you too, Sandy!
- 哦，你也不是，桑迪！
He's standing right there!
他就站在那里！
Well, I'm sorry, SpongeBob,
but I don't see anyone.
好吧，对不起，海绵宝宝，
但我没有看到任何人。
- He's the giant hamster,
right there!
- 他是巨型仓鼠
就在那里！
- Oh, I get it.
- 哦，我明白了。
He's your imaginary friend.
他是你想象中的朋友。
- But he's not imaginary.
He's real!
- 但他不是想象出来的。
他是真实的！
- Oh, no need to get
so fiery, SpongeBob.
-哦，没必要得到
如此火热，海绵宝宝。
It's okay to have
an imaginary friend.
拥有就好了
一个想象中的朋友。
Lots of people do.
很多人都这样做。
You two have fun now, ya hear?
你们两个现在玩得很开心，听到了吗？
I was so excited
to introduce you to my friends,
我很兴奋
把你介绍给我的朋友们，
but now they're all
acting strange.
但现在他们都
表现得很奇怪。
- I hate to see ya
so upset, SpongeBob.
- 我讨厌见到你
海绵宝宝，好难过啊
But take heart.
但请放心。
There's a reason
your friends can't see me.
这是有原因的
你的朋友看不到我。
- Of course!
- 当然！
Unlike you, they never ate
the magic sandwich.
与你不同，他们从不吃东西
神奇的三明治。
What magic sandwich?
什么神奇三明治？
- Why, the one that's
as fuzzy as me, of course.
- 为什么，就是那个
当然，和我一样模糊。
- You mean the moldy
Krabby Patty I found at work?
- 你是说发霉的
我在工作中发现的蟹黄派蒂？
- You say moldy Krabby Patty,
- 你说发霉的克拉比帕蒂，
I say magic sandwich.
我说魔法三明治。
- Hmm...
- 唔...
Maybe I should share my magic
sandwich with my friends.
也许我应该分享我的魔法
和我的朋友们一起吃三明治。
That way, they can see you,
and see how awesome you are!
这样他们就能看到你
看看你有多棒！
- Yes! Let them witness
my fuzzy tummy.
- 是的！让他们见证
我毛茸茸的肚子。
Tummy...
肚子...
- Tummy, tummy,
tummy, tummy, tummy.
- 肚子，肚子，
肚子，肚子，肚子。
There! Enough for everyone.
那里！对每个人来说都足够了。
- Excellent, SpongeBob.
- 太棒了，海绵宝宝。
Okay, let's go.
好吧，我们走吧。
Aged Krabby Patties here!
老蟹肉饼来啦！
Get your artisanal aged
Krabby Patties here!
让您的手工艺品老化
蟹肉饼来啦！
Did I mention they were free?
我有没有提到它们是免费的？
Do you see Cuddle E. Hugs?
你看到拥抱 E. 拥抱了吗？
Yes!
是的！
Oh, he's glorious!
哦，他是荣耀的！
- Yeah, his fur looks silkier
than actual silk.
- 是的，他的皮毛看起来更丝滑
比真正的丝绸。
- Yes, make them
all see me, SpongeBob!
- 是的，制作它们
大家都来看我吧，海绵宝宝！
Make them all see,
Cuddle E. Hugs.
让他们都看到，
拥抱E。拥抱。
- SpongeBob, what are you doing
giving away free food?
- 海绵宝宝，你在做什么
赠送免费食物？
Are you cra--
你是不是——
I can't resist the fuzzy.
我无法抗拒模糊。
Come, everyone,
来吧，大家，
and hug your new best friend!
拥抱你最好的新朋友！
- No, Cuddle E. Hugs, no!
- 不，拥抱E。拥抱，不！
- Yes, SpongeBob
SquarePants, yes!
- 是的，海绵宝宝
方裤，是的！
- Sorry, I'm late, I...
- 对不起，我迟到了，我...
Um... back to bed.
嗯……回到床上去。
I thought we were friends!
我以为我们是朋友！
What happened?
发生了什么？
Oh...
哦...
Well, your friend ate me
is what happened.
好吧，你的朋友吃了我
发生了什么事。
Not cool!
不酷！
Yeah, grumble!
是啊，发牢骚！
- Sorry, everyone.
- 对不起，大家。
- You need to
imagine your friends
- 你需要
想象你的朋友
more carefully, SpongeBob.
更仔细一点，海绵宝宝。
- I just don't get it.
- 我就是不明白。
Why did he act like that
last night?
他为什么这么做
昨晚？
I thought we were BFFs.
我以为我们是好朋友。
I need to talk to him.
我需要和他谈谈。
- Crazy time last night,
right, bro?
- 昨晚的疯狂时光，
对吧，兄弟？
- Don't "bro" me,
Cuddle E. Hugs.
- 别跟我说“兄弟”
拥抱E。拥抱。
You embarrassed me last night,
and you ate all my friends!
昨晚你让我尴尬了
你还吃了我所有的朋友！
Why would you do that?
你为什么要这么做？
- Didn't you ever wonder
- 你有没有想过
what the E in my name
stands for?
我名字中的E是什么
代表？
It's Eat!
是吃！
I'm always hungry, ya know?
我总是很饿，你知道吗？
- Oh!
Well, why didn't you say so?
- 哦！
嗯，你为什么不这么说呢？
Here, have the last
of my Patty.
在这里，还有最后的
我的帕蒂。
Wait, no! No!
等等，不！不！
What?
什么？
Oh, pellets.
哦，颗粒。